[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these does a positive hydrogen ion lack?", "correct_answer": "Electrons and neutrons", "incorrect_answers": ["Neutrons", "Electrons", "Protons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names refers to the precious stone morganite?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cesian beryl", "Pink emerald", "Rose beryl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1981 movie was honored with a Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture.", "correct_answer": "Mommie Dearest", "incorrect_answers": ["Endless Love", "Tarzan, the Ape Man", "The Legend of the Lone Ranger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these organelles is a part of the endomembrane system of eukaryotic cells?", "correct_answer": "Endoplasmic reticulum", "incorrect_answers": ["Chloroplast", "Mitochondrion", "Nucleus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2005 hurricane season, there were 13 hurricanes of the overall number of 27 registered storms, which broke the record of 12, set in 1969.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the note the kids leave with the babysitters body in the movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead:\n____________________ inside. Died of natural causes.", "correct_answer": "Nice old lady", "incorrect_answers": ["The babysitter is", "Our mother is", "We dont know who is"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Americas entry into World War Two led to a ban on sliced bread starting in August 1943.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did the movie Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl come out in 2003?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fireflies are known for their ability to produce light of this color.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Pale red", "Green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Along with Neil  Armstrong and Michael Collins, who was the third member of the Apollo 11 crew?", "correct_answer": "Buzz Aldrin", "incorrect_answers": ["James A. Lovell, Jr", "William Anders", "Fred Haise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although it is generally described as a transparent liquid, in seas, lakes and other large water bodies, water appears blue.  What property of water is this attributed to?", "correct_answer": "Water absorbs light in the red range", "incorrect_answers": ["Water reflects light in the red range", "Water refracts light", "Water radiates in the blue range"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word volcano comes from the name of the Roman god of fire, Vulcan. Who is the analogue of Vulcan in Greek mythology?", "correct_answer": "Hephaestus", "incorrect_answers": ["Helios", "Hermes", "Zeus"]}]